A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 3 FA1218
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1908-1999; 3
  - New York University Medical Center, Hyperbaric Medicine: H. Rusk (791-B), 1971-1974 (Box 289, Folder 2136)
  - New York University Medical Center, Hyperbaric Medicine: T. Reich-H. Rusk (74-149) (791-C), 1974-1977 (Box 289, Folder 2137)
  - Presbyterian-University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, Erythropoiesis: F. Gardner (74-175) (751-B), 1974-1976 (Box 289, Folder 2138-2140)
  - Project Hear, Ear transplants: R. Perkins (74-184) (753-B), 1974-1977 (Box 289, Folder 2141)
  - Royal Victoria Hospital, Transplant immunology: R. Guttman (74-204) (757-C), 1971-1973 (Box 289, Folder 2142)
  - St. Luke's Hospital, Coenzyme Q: T. Van Itallie (262), 1963-1965 (Box 289, Folder 2143)
  - Stanford Research Institute, Pesticide residue: O. Senn (273), 1961-1964 (Box 289, Folder 2144-2145)
  - Stanford University, Acoustic microscopy: C. Quate (74-237), 1974-1976 (Box 290, Folder 2146-2147)
  - Tufts University, Venous thrombosis: M. Hume (74-243), 1974-1946 (Box 290, Folder 2148)
  - University of Oregon, Measles: J. Hallum (74-285), 1974-1976 (Box 290, Folder 2149)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch, Diabetes mellitus: L. Stout (74-316) (840-D), 1974-1976 (Box 290, Folder 2150)
  - Vanderbilt University Hospital and School of Medicine, ACTH secretion: G. Liddle (no grant number), 1960 (Box 290, Folder 2151)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 290, Folder 2152-2153)
  - Washington University, Antifungal-viral therapy: G. Medoff (850), 1971-1974 (Box 291, Folder 2154)
  - Alliance to Save Energy: D. Norland (82-683), 1980-1985 (Box 291, Folder 2155-2160)
  - Alliance to Save Energy: D. Norland (82-683), 1980-1985 (Box 292, Folder 2161-2166)
  - Alliance to Save Energy: D. Norland (82-683) Separated media "EIMS Demo Disks", 1985 October 7; 2014:023:020; 3 5.25-inch computer disks
  - Alliance to Save Energy: D. Norland (82-683) Separated media "EIMS Programs"
  - Alliance to Save Energy: D. Norland (82-683) Separated media "EIMS Data Entry"
  - East Carolina University: D. Hawkins (RFP-131, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2167)
  - East Tennessee Baptist Hospital: J. Greene (RFP-122, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2168)
  - Elderplan, Inc.: D. Kodner (RFP-177, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2169)
  - Emory University: M. Lubin (RFP-119, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2170)
  - Florida A and M University: G Blyden (RFP-175, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2171)
  - Fort Bend Eye Foundation: D. Barron (RFP-140, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2172)
  - Foundation for the Brain: M. Storfer (RFP-053, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2173)
  - Georgetown University: M. Dubois (RFP-083, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2174)
  - Georgia State University: W. Richardson (RFP-024, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2175)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital: R. Dalton (RFP-078, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2176)
  - Greater Health Cooperative of Puget Sound: E. Wagner (RFP-153, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 293, Folder 2177)
  - Hamilton Avenue Family Health Center: G. Matthew (RFP-159, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2178)
  - Holy Family Manor: D. Rigney (RFP-167, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2179)
  - Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania: G. Gibson (RFP-160, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2180)
  - Hudson Valley Poison Center: S. Oransky (RFP-019, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2181)
  - Huntington Memorial Hospital: M. White (RFP-088, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2182)
  - Idaho State University: R. Bowen (RFP-013, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2183)
  - Indiana University School of Medicine: J. Darnell (RFP-118, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2184)
  - Iowa-Illinois Health Care Alliance: R. Lee (RFP-026, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2185)
  - Jefferson County (Alabama) Commission: B. Bonfield (RFP-202, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2186)
  - Jewish Hospital of St. Louis: S. Birge (RFP-194, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2187)
  - Jewish Hospital of St. Louis: T. Lackner (RFP-209, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2188)
  - Jewish Institute for Geriatric Care: D. Glaser (RFP-075, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 294, Folder 2189)
  - Johns Hopkins University: P. German (RFP-135, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2190)
  - Johns Hopkins School: L. Tune (RFP-076, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2191)
  - Kaiser Foundation Hospital: R. Johnson (RFP-030, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2192)
  - Kennesaw College: A. Bairan (RFP-049, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2193)
  - Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center: S. Greenberg (RFP-191, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2194)
  - Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center: S. Baroth (RFP-208, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2195)
  - Leonard Morse Hospital: J. Wiesendanger (RFP-151, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2196)
  - Lifespan, Inc.: C. Peterson (RFP-117, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2197)
  - Long Island Jewish Medical Center: R. Blum (RFP-046, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2198)
  - Long Island University: J. Sciarra (RFP-079, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2199)
  - Lutheran General Foundation: M. Rudin (RFP-162, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2200)
  - Lutheran Hospitals: R. O'Neill (RFP-205, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 2201)
  - Mary Immaculate Nursing Home: B. McNabb (RFP-016, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2202)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital: A. Jette (RFP-091, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2203)
  - McKennan Hospital: J. Paulson (RFP-104, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2204)
  - Medford Leas: L. Forrest (RFP-006, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2205)
  - Medical College of Ohio: C. Proefrock (RFP-115, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2206)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania: I. Katz (RFP-127, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2207)
  - Medical Univesity of South Carolina: C. Brock (RFP-037, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2208)
  - Medical College of Wisconsin: T. Garland (RFP-103, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2209)
  - Missouri Department of Health: B. Rikard (RFP-012, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 296, Folder 2210)
  - Mercer University: R. Anderson (RFP-108, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2211)
  - Mercy Regional Medical Center: D. Mendoza Freeman (RFP-023, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2212)
  - Methodist Hospital (Houston): L. Glantz-Miller (RFP-180, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2213)
  - Middlesex County (Massachusetts) Hospital: K. Bird (RFP-001, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2214)
  - Millard Fillmore Hospital: J. Jennings (RFP-176, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2215)
  - Missouri Department of Social Services: L. Conley (RFP-138, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2216)
  - Montefiore Medical Center: R. Kennedy (RFP-129, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2217)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center (Chicago): R. Rothstein (RFP-061, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2218)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center (New York): R. Adelman (RFP-132, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2219)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center (Florida): D. Spivack (RFP-148, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 297, Folder 2220)
  - Nathan S. Kline Institute: J. Zito (RFP-112, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2221)
  - National Council on the Aging: J. Ossofsky (RFP-102, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2222)
  - New England Institute for Healthcare Service Research, Inc.: R. Murphy (RFP-158, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2223)
  - New Hampshire Pharmaceutical Association: F. Case (RFP-011, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2224)
  - New Mexico State University: J. Youngers (RFP-161, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2225)
  - New York Medical College: J. Freiser (RFP-133, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2226)
  - New York University Medical Center: B. Reisberg (RFP-096, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2227)
  - New York State Department of Health and Office for the Aging: N. Santiago (RFP-141, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2228)
  - Northwestern University: G. Goldberger (RFP-047, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2229)
  - Oakwood Hospital: R. Linton (RFP-182, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 299, Folder 2230)
  - Ohio State Department of Health: T. Halpin (RFP-48, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 299, Folder 2231)
  - On Lok Senior Health Services: R. Zawadski (RFP-203, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 299, Folder 2232)
  - Oregon State University: W. Simonson (RFP-186, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 299, Folder 2233)
  - Grant-Making Summaries, 1970-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2234)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, A-Ch, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2235)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, Ch-Je, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2236)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, Jo-Mi, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2237)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, Mo-Sl, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2238)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, St-T, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2239)
  - Grant Applications and Summaries, U-Y, 1969-1977 (Box 299, Folder 2240)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, A-B, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2241)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, C-D, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2242)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, E-H, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2243)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, I-L, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2244)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, M, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2245)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, N-O, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2246)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, P, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2247)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, R-S, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2248)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, T, 1954-1974 (Box 300, Folder 2249)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, United-University M, 1954-1974 (Box 301, Folder 2250)
  - Summaries of Closed Grants, University N-Younger, 1954-1974 (Box 301, Folder 2251)
  - Income, Appropriations, and Major Grants, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2252)
  - Grant Summaries, A-B, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2253)
  - Grant Summaries, C, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2254)
  - Grant Summaries, D-G, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2255)
  - Grant Summaries, H-I, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2256)
  - Grant Summaries, J-L, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2257)
  - Grant Summaries, Ma, 1954-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2258)
  - Grant Summaries, Mc-Mu, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2259)
  - Grant Summaries, N-O, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2260)
  - Grant Summaries, P, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2261)
  - Grant Summaries, R, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2262)
  - Grant Summaries, S, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2263)
  - Grant Summaries, T-University Hospital, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2264)
  - Grant Summaries, University of A-W, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2265)
  - Grant Summaries, V-Y, 1954-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2266)
  - University of California, San Francisco, Malabsorption-Pancreas: M. Sleisenger (77-093), 1977-1980 (Box 303, Folder 2267)
  - University of Cincinnati College of Medicine, Ischemia: E. Jacobson (77-253), 1977-180 (Box 303, Folder 2268)
  - University of Florida College of Medicine: A. Gasset (229), 1972-1979 (Box 303, Folder 2269)
  - University of Illinois, Prostaglandins: D. Wilson (76-126), 1976-1980 (Box 303, Folder 2270)
  - University of Maryland School of Medicine, Tuberculosis test: Z. Reggiardo (76-282), 1976-1979 (Box 303, Folder 2271)
  - University of Miami, Infections: K. Miller (74-436), 1947-1979 (Box 303, Folder 2272)
  - University of Miami, Pulmonary function: J. Ryan (76-136), 1976-1980 (Box 303, Folder 2273)
  - University of Oregon Medical School: G. Leslie (74-296), 1974-1978 (Box 303, Folder 2274)
  - University of Oregon Health Sciences Center, Interferon: J. Hallum (77-037), 1977-1980 (Box 303, Folder 2275)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Bad blood cells: H. Sloviter (76-145), 1976-1978 (Box 304, Folder 2276)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Red cell substitute: H. Sloviter (78-036), 1978-1982 (Box 304, Folder 2277)
  - University of Pittsburgh: S. Yao (77-073), 1977-1981 (Box 304, Folder 2278)
  - University of Texas at Austin, Coenzyme Q: K. Folkers (74-476), 1974-1978 (Box 304, Folder 2279)
  - University of Texas, Dallas, Pharmacology-Infant: G. McCracken (76-156), 1976-1979 (Box 304, Folder 2280)
  - University of Texas, Galveston, Diabetes: L. Stout (76-227), 1976-1980 (Box 304, Folder 2281)
  - University of Texas, Galveston, Gastric ulcer: J. Thompson (77-103), 1977-1980 (Box 304, Folder 2282)
  - University of Texas, Galveston, Anemia dialysis: F. Gardner (77-342), 1977-1981 (Box 304, Folder 2283)
  - University of Virginia: J. Davis (74-466), 1974-1978 (Box 304, Folder 2284)
  - Vanderbilt University, Thyroid hormones: E. Siegel (76-166), 1976-1980 (Box 305, Folder 2285)
  - Vanderbilt University School of Medicine: Z. McGee (77-263), 1977-1981 (Box 305, Folder 2286)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, Cerebral circulation: W. Rosenblum (76-176), 1976-1982 (Box 305, Folder 2287)
  - Washington University School of Medicine, Fungal: G. Medoff (77-196), 1977-1982 (Box 305, Folder 2288)
  - Boston University: R. Egdahll (79-049-3H), 1978-1980 (Box 305, Folder 2289-2291)
  - Health Services Foundation (79-013-2H), 1978-1980 (Box 306, Folder 2292-2295)
  - Interstudy: W. McClure (79-022), 1978-1981 (Box 306, Folder 2296-2298)
  - Johns Hopkins University: C. Schramm (79-012), 1979-1981 (Box 307, Folder 2299-2301)
  - Rochester Area Hospitals Corporation: J. Block (79-001), 1979-1980 (Box 307, Folder 2302)
  - St. Luke's-Roosevelt Hospital (80-327-2H), 1980-1981 (Box 307, Folder 2303-2304)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 308, Folder 2305-2309)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 309, Folder 2310-2313)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 310, Folder 2314)
  - Johns Hopkins School of Medicine, Parkinson's Disease: S. Snyder (77-146), 1977-1984 (Box 310, Folder 2315)
  - Stanford University, Liver disease: P. Gregory (76-273), 1976-1983 (Box 310, Folder 2316)
  - Webb-Waring Lung Institute, AntiB vaccine: A. Crowle (77-273), 1977-1981 (Box 310, Folder 2317)
  - Westchester County Medical Center, Electrical seizure relief: I. Cooper (77-353), 1977-1981 (Box 310, Folder 2318)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, Endotoxins: S. Watson (77-113), 1977-1981 (Box 310, Folder 2319)
  - New York Community Trust: H. West (80-264), 1980-1982 (Box 311, Folder 2320-2322)
  - New York University School of Law: D. Schoenbrod (80-526), 1980-1982 (Box 311, Folder 2323-2324)
  - New York Zoological Society: H. Phipps (83-066), 1983-1984 (Box 311, Folder 2325-2326)
  - Ohio River Valley Sanitation Commission-Council of State Governments: L. Weaver (80-441), 1980-1982 (Box 312, Folder 2327-2331)
  - Rand Corporation: J. Acton (80-210), 1980-1984 (Box 312, Folder 2332-2333)
  - Rand Corporation: J. Acton (80-210), 1980-1984 (Box 313, Folder 2334-2338)
  - Association of Physical Plant Administrators: C. Crittenden (81-109), 1981-1984 (Box 313, Folder 2339)
  - Association of Physical Plant Administrators: C. Crittenden (81-109), 1981-1984 (Box 314, Folder 2340-2344)
  - Association of Physical Plant Administrators: (82-626), 1982-1985 (Box 315, Folder 2345-2350)
  - Alliance to Save Energy: J. Wolf (80-338), 1980-1984 (Box 316, Folder 2351-2357)
  - Alliance to Save Energy: J. Wolf (80-338), 1980-1984 (Box 317, Folder 2358-2359)
  - Brooklyn Energy Program: R. Harmon (80-382), 1980-1983 (Box 317, Folder 2360-2361)
  - Environmental Mediation International: R. Stein (81-002), 1981-1982 (Box 317, Folder 2362-2363)
  - Environmental Mediation International: R. Stein (81-002), 1981-1982 (Box 318, Folder 2364-2365)
  - Georgetown University: Price (81-376) (Box 318, Folder 2366-2369)
  - Health Services Improvement Fund Inc.: K. Weiner (80-137), 1980-1983 (Box 318, Folder 2370)
  - Health Services Improvement Fund Inc.: K. Weiner (80-137), 1980-1983 (Box 319, Folder 2371-2372)
  - The Hospital Research and Educational Trust: M. Gough (81-240), 1981-1984 (Box 319, Folder 2373-2377)
  - MASBO Cooperative Corporation: R. Pritchard (80-207), 1980-1983 (Box 320, Folder 2378-2380)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: L. Cox (80-188), 1980-1983 (Box 320, Folder 2381-2382)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: C. Flanigan (80-252), 1980-1983 (Box 320, Folder 2383)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: C. Flanigan (80-252), 1980-1983 (Box 321, Folder 2384-2388)
  - New York University School of Law: D. Schoenbrod (81-032), 1980-1982 (Box 321, Folder 2389)
  - Massachusetts Hospital Association: L. Kushins (82-636), 1982-1984 (Box 322, Folder 2390-2395)
  - Maternity Center Association: R. Lubic (83-016), 1983-1984 (Box 322, Folder 2396)
  - Mercy Hospital: K. Popko (80-297), 1980-1982 (Box 323, Folder 2397-2398)
  - Metropolitan Opera: J. Smith (82-694), 1982-1983 (Box 323, Folder 2399)
  - Midpeninsula Health Service: J. Ewy (83-103), 1983-1985 (Box 323, Folder 2400-2401)
  - Morningside Community Hospital Association: L. Pipes (79-009), 1979-1981 (Box 323, Folder 2402-2404)
  - National Executive Service Corps: D. Clark (82-569), 1982-1985 (Box 324, Folder 2405-2407)
  - Albany Medical College: D. Jue (RFP-150, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2408)
  - Alexandria, Virginia, Taskforce on Medications: L. Rubenstein (RFP-200, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2409)
  - Amherst Medical Associates: A. Larkin (RFP-055, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2410)
  - Anchorage Neighborhood Health Center: T. DeLap (RFP-022, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2411)
  - Austin-Travis County Health Department: M. Candelas (RFP-173, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2412)
  - Stephen Baroth (RFP-210, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2413)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: J. Merrill (RFP-192, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 324, Folder 2414)
  - Beth Israel Hospital and Geriatric Center: L. Metzger (RFP-100, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2415)
  - Bethesda General Hospital: J. Norwood (RFP-169, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2416)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts: P. Gillette (RFP-002, decline), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2417)
  - Boone County (Indiana) Senior Services: M. Corson (RFP-166, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2418)
  - Boston University Medical Center: P. Barry (RFP-095, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2419)
  - Boston University Medical Center: R. Friedman (RFP-121, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2420)
  - Boston University School of Medicine: R. Meenan (RFP-206, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2421)
  - Botsford General Hospital: R. Wetmore (RFP-087, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2422)
  - Bowman Gray School of Medicine: J. Pharris (RFP-114, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2423)
  - Brown University: M. Fretwell (RFP-144, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2424)
  - Burbank Hospital: D. Sevigny (RFP-098, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 2425)
  - California Health Planning Association: K. Mason (RFP-010, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2426)
  - Case Western Reserve University: J. Kowal (RFP-168, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2427)
  - Catholic University: C. Smoley (RFP-171, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2428)
  - Center for Advanced Rehabilitation Engineering: G. Kondraske (RFP-099, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2429)
  - Center for Advanced Studies in Gerontology and Nutrition: J. Vitale (RFP-106, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2430)
  - Center for Geriatric Care: J. Ryan (RFP-060, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2431)
  - Center for Public Representation: S. Schwartz (RFP-065, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2432)
  - Charles R. Drew Postgraduate Medical School: L. Creary (RFP-145, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2433)
  - Chelsea Community Hospital: L. Perkins (RFP-058, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2434)
  - Choate-Symmes Health Services: S. Saleeba (RFP-059, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2435)
  - City of New York Department of Aging: J. Sainer (RFP-018, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2436)
  - College of Physicians and Surgeons of Columbia University: S. Shea (RFP-039, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2437)
  - Colorado Department of Health: H. Meadows (RFP-063, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2438)
  - Columbia Hospital: D. Hay (RFP-154, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2439)
  - Consumer Health Initiative: F. Wegner (RFP-211, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2440)
  - Cornell University: C. Fay (RFP-070, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2441)
  - COSSMHO: J. Delgado (RFP-137, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2442)
  - County of Los Angeles, High Desert Hospital: H. Glenchur (RFP-004, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2443)
  - Daughters of Miriam Center for the Aged: H. Adelsburg (RFP-092, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2444)
  - Dede Wallace Center: J. Flor (RFP-035, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2445)
  - Drake University: H. Martens (RFP-062, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2446)
  - Duke University Medicine Center: W. Anlyan (RFP-111, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 327, Folder 2447)
  - Duke University Medicine Center: W. Anlyan (RFP-107, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2448)
  - Florida Alcohol and Drug Abuse Association: J. Daigle (RFP-067, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2449)
  - Southern Illinois University: J. Kvale (RFP-134, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2450)
  - Southwestern Pennsylvania Area Agency on Aging: D. Goughler (RFP-057, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2451)
  - St. Elizabeth Medical Center: C. Wilkins (RFP-056, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2452)
  - St. Francis Medical Center: M. Flaherty (RFP-097, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2453)
  - St. John's Hospital: J. Whitmer (RFP-197, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2454)
  - St. Joseph Hospital: T. Domenici (RFP-008, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 328, Folder 2455)
  - St. Louis Drug Information Center: D. Butler (RFP-213, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2456)
  - St. Luke's Hospitals: R. Perry (RFP-184, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2457)
  - St. Luke's Roosevelt Hospital Center: T. Van Itallie (RFP-165, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2458)
  - St. Margaret Memorial Hospital: M. Takach (RFP-174, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2459)
  - St. Mary's Hospital: M. Clifford (RFP-185, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2460)
  - St. Paul-Ramsey Medical Center: D. Brundage (RFP-014, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2461)
  - St. Paul-Ramsey Medical Center: G. Tollefson (RFP-126, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2462)
  - St. Vincent Medical Center: J. Ross (RFP-201, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2463)
  - St Vincent's Medical Center: P. Zaenger (RFP-041, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2464)
  - Stanford University Medical Center: P. Rudd (RFP-028, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2465)
  - Stanford University: F. Gustafson (RFP-082, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2466)
  - State of Minnesota Department of Human Services: L. Levine (RFP-074, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 329, Folder 2467)
  - Stonybrook Research Foundation: L. Capobianco (RFP-027, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2468)
  - Syracuse University: M. Charters (RFP-015, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2469)
  - Temple University: A. Finestone (RFP-050, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2470)
  - Texas College of Osteopathic Medicine: C. Maxvill (RFP-155, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2471)
  - Texas Tech University: G. House (RFP-123, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2472)
  - Texas Woman's University: D. Walsh (RFP 093, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2473)